Workplace Competition Code
职场竞赛守则
Don’t cry in front of me again
以后不准在我面前哭
Never negotiate with tears
绝对不要用眼泪来协商
That's the worst way
那是最糟的方式
I think it’s great to be loud
自以為大聲就了不起
You get off work
你下班吧
(Singing karaoke)
（歡唱卡啦OK）
-(The way you stare at me)
-（你凝視我的眼神）
- (Nothing more to say) - (Nothing to say more)
-（無須多說）
-(I want to be our last)
-（我要為我們的最後）
- (be prepared)
-（做好準備）
Time is wasted
時間都浪費掉了
If you want to curse, you can curse. Now is the time.
你想罵人就罵吧，現在正是時候
bad woman
壞女人
Do you have to say it so harshly?
一定要把話說得那麼難聽嗎？
Hey, I'm so weak
喂，太有氣無力了
Your scolding is too bland
你罵得太平淡了
Bad stinky woman
惡劣的臭女人
Does she think she is great?
她自以為了不起啊？
Yes, this is better
不錯，這樣有好一點
How could she treat my eight years of work experience like dirt?
她怎麼可以把我八年的 工作經歷視如糞土？
How can I be the same as the newcomer?
我和新人怎麼會一樣？
Really
真是的
I came in based on work experience.
我是靠工作經驗進來的
Right?
对吧？
The competition rate for special recruitment is exaggerated, right?
特別招聘的競爭率很誇張的吧？
Yeah, of course
是啊，那當然
I must prove it to her
我一定要證明給她看
I have to prove how serious I am!
我一定要證明我有多認真！
Then again
話又說回來
Why do I cry so much?
我為什麼這麼愛哭呢？
I always shed tears involuntarily
我總會不由自主地流眼淚
I can't control myself when I feel wronged
一覺得委屈就控制不住
That makes me even more angry and upset
那更令我生氣懊惱
Some people say tears and smiles are the same
有人說眼淚和笑容是一樣的
So don’t feel wronged just because you cry easily.
所以你別因為容易哭就覺得委屈
You love to laugh and cry
你愛笑又愛哭
Just be true to your feelings
只是忠於自己的感受
Who told you to be so handsome?
這麼帥氣的話是誰告訴你的？
it is me
就是我
Very stylish, right?
很有型吧？
("An Ordinary Day")
（《平凡的一天》）
If you dare to ruin the atmosphere, I will kill you!
你敢破壞氣氛，小心我殺了你！
("The Horse Runs")
（《馬兒奔跑吧》）
(This is how life is in the world)
（人生在世就是如此）
-(Shut up!)
-（閉嘴！）
- (Comrades, for my country)
-（戰友們，為我的國家）
- (Fight with your life)
-（賭上性命而戰）
morning
早晨
Hello
你好
Agent Park Yun-soo
朴允昭代理
Yes, team leader
是，组长
Agent Park, this is your PR schedule.
朴代理，這是你的公關日程表
Also, please contact the Human Resources Office to get the PC as soon as possible
還有，請你聯絡人力資源室 儘快拿到個人電腦
If you don't push it, this matter will continue to drag on.
不催促一下，這件事會不停地拖下去
yes
是
(Qualifications are not limited, recruitment of experienced personnel will be finalized, public relations schedule)
（資格不拘，具經驗人員招聘 最終錄取者，公關日程表）
Hello everyone
大家好
I just joined the Public Relations Team 3 of the Public Relations Office of the Business Strategy Headquarters.
我是剛加入經營策略本部 公關室公關三組的
Park Yoon Joo
朴允珠
Why did you come to apply for Shi Yong’s special recruitment?
你為什麼會來應徵 世容的特別招聘呢？
I have ambition
我有了野心
I want to have my own brand within a big company
我想在大企業內擁有自己的品牌
Many people are quite curious about your past experiences
許多人相當好奇你過去的經歷
Can you share your experience and how you started working in PR?
可以分享一下你的經歷 和開始從事公關行業的契機嗎？
I used to go to a technical high school
我以前是讀技術型高中
After graduation, I worked in the general affairs team
畢業後就在總務組工作
It took about three to four years
大概做了三至四年
Later I moved to a room…
後來換到一間…
Hello
你好
Yes, please take care of me
是，請多多關照
-Is it okay to just sit here? -right
-坐在這裡就可以了嗎？ -對
It's time to start shooting. Maintain this position and don't move.
要開始拍了，維持這個姿勢不要動
Take some more pictures
再拍幾張
Like this?
像這樣嗎？
Yes, good, very good now
對，很好，現在非常好
take this
拿著這個
Smile a little wider
笑開一點
Slowly jump to the next one
慢慢跳下一張
-Thank you for your hard work -No.
-辛苦了 -不會
Wait, go back to the previous one
等等，回去上一張
How about this one? I feel it's ok
這張怎麼樣？我覺得還不錯
Yes, pretty good
對，挺不錯的
This one is very good
這張很好
Let’s pick this one up first and let’s continue reading.
這張先挑起來，我們繼續看
-If you like it, tell me . -Wait a minute, the previous picture of this one
-有喜歡的就告訴我 -等一下，這個的上一張
-This one? -right
-這張嗎？ -對
Nice shot
拍得不錯
You feel…
你覺得…
how do you feel?
你覺得如何？
nice
不錯啊
very good
很好
There are too many good photos
好的照片太多了
she behaved well
她表現得很好
Hello
喂
I work so hard and you just give me a lunch?
我這麼辛苦地工作 你只用便當打發我嗎？
Go report it to the Ministry of Labor?
你去跟勞動部舉報啊
I just joined the company and you want to ask me to leave?
我才剛進公司就想叫我走人啊？
Of course we can't fire you so quickly
當然不能這麼快就開除你
Don't be too afraid
不用太害怕
It's a bit exaggerated to cause trouble over this bento.
為了這一個便當滋生事端 有點太誇張了
It’s my favorite bento
是我最愛的便當啊
So what do you eat?
那你吃什麼？
You also know that I don't like eels
你也知道我不愛吃鰻魚
The eel looks disgusting
鰻魚的外型很噁心
Keep up the good work when you’re full, Yun Zhao
吃飽要繼續加油，允昭
We still have to be busy later
我們之後還有得忙
I am also in public relations, I know very well
我也是做公關的，我很清楚
Remember to say something if it goes too far
太過頭記得說一聲
So what if I say it?
說了又能怎樣？
I hope you will at least say it
我是希望你最起碼要說出來
The same goes for everyone going to see a psychiatrist.
大家去看精神科醫生也是同樣的道理
It's important to express it
表達出來是很重要的
(Inauguration ceremony for blind hiring of new employees regardless of qualifications)
（資格不拘盲聘新進員工就職儀式）
(You will lead the future of Serong and we support your dreams and passion)
（各位將引領世容的未來 我們支持你們的夢想與熱情）
(Inaugural ceremony for new employees in 2022)
（2022年度新進員工就職儀式）
Hello
你好
Reporter Park
朴記者
Please give me some advice
请多多指教
Sit down
坐啊
OK
好的
You have to be as formal as you are at work, right?
你要像在工作那麼拘謹吧？
Yes, we are working
對，我們是在工作
Pour us a cup of tea
幫我們倒杯茶
yes
是
Are you still used to staying in hotels?
酒店住得還習慣嗎？
This one is okay
這個啊，還可以
Then you can continue to live here so that I can have friends who live nearby.
那你就繼續住 這樣我就有住在附近的朋友了
we are not friends
我們不是朋友
It's been a while
已經有一段時間了
Really high maintenance
真是難伺候
so
所以
Have you met Ahn Eun-seok?
你見過安恩錫了嗎？
You haven't met yet?
你們還沒見過面啊？
I have no reason to see him
我沒有理由見他
That's right, why would you go to your ex-husband if you have nothing to do?
也對，沒事去找前夫做什麼？
You have a daughter, right?
你有個女兒吧？
Have you met your daughter? How old is she? I remember it was written in your profile
你有見到女兒嗎？她幾歲了？ 我記得你的資料裡有寫
represent
代表
I hired you because I wanted someone to chat with me.
我聘用你是希望有人能陪我聊天
Is that my responsibility? Yeah?
那是我分內的事嗎？是嗎？
Message from the Vice President
副社長的話
You should think so
應該會這麼想吧
She is an ESG professional consultant
她是ESG專業顧問
(ESG: refers to environmental protection, social responsibility and corporate governance)
（ESG：意指環境保護 社會責任與公司治理）
(Non-financial standards for business operations)
（為企業營運的非財務性標準）
(ESG expert, Koo Yi-jung)
（ESG專家，具伊貞）
ESG？
ESG？
It should be considered as if she hired a consultant.
應該能當作她請了一名顧問來就好
Representation is indeed a lonely position
代表確實是一個孤獨的職位
It's good to have someone to talk to.
有個說話的伴也好
yes
是啊
Vice president, you should make preparations now
副社長，你現在該做準備了
-Then let's go -Yes
-那我們走吧 -是
You're the only male, so sit in the middle
你是唯一的男性，所以坐正中間
Come, this way please
來，這邊請
Please take a seat…
請坐…
hateful
可惡
- Jae Min, let me check the list of reporters - Okay
-才旻，我看一下記者名單 -好的
-Have you contacted everyone? -yes
-你聯絡到所有人了吧？ -是
Only Y News didn’t answer the phone
只有Y新聞沒聽電話
Really, why haven't they come yet?
真是的，他們怎麼還不來？
Hello
喂
smile
笑一下
This is the leader of the second public relations team
這位是公關二組組長
I am Song Xuantai
我是宋宣泰
That one is the head of the public relations team
那位是公關一組組長
Hello, I am Cui Yonghao
你好，我是崔永皓
That's the leader of the third public relations team
那位是公關三組組長
Hello, my name is Chi Yinzhen
你好，我叫池銀禎
Nice to meet you all, my name is Goo Yi Jung
很高興認識各位，我是具伊貞
nice to meet you
很榮幸見到你
(You will lead the future of Serong. We support your dreams and passion)
（各位将引领世容的未来 我们支持你们的梦想与热情）
(No qualifications required! Blind hiring)
（資格不拘！盲聘）
Who planned this plan?
這個計劃是誰策劃的？
Hey, Jae Min
喂，才旻
He is the planner of this project with no restrictions on qualifications
他是本次資格不拘計劃的策劃人
and business undertaker
及業務承辦人
I’m Yoo Jae-min from the Public Relations Team 2
我是公關二組的柳才旻
You also seem to think that this kind of activity helps promote
你似乎還認為這種活動有助於宣傳
This requires a lot of effort
這需要投入許多力氣
but not much effect
卻不見太大成效
This is done to improve Se Yong’s image
這麼做是為了提升世容的形象
-Is it right? -Yes
-對嗎？ -是的
This kind of superficial and short-lived activity
這種做表面工夫又曇花一現的活動
Already a bit outdated
已經有點過時了
Then please let the event continue
那請你讓活動能持續下去吧
The Republic of Korea holds a Fair Recruitment Fair every year hosted by the Ministry
大韓民國每年都會由僱傭勞動部 主辦舉行公平招聘
and blind hiring excellence case competition
和盲聘的卓越案例競賽
Although most of them are registered for government agencies,
雖然多數為政府機關報名參賽
However, it can be seen that the social demand for fair recruitment based on work ability
但由此可見，根據工作能力 公平招聘的社會需求
is big
是很大的
-Per year? -Yes
-每年？ -是的
What if it can continue?
若能持續下去呢？
- that's a good thing of course - no
-那當然是一件好事 -不
-This is not the answer I want -Director Goo
-這不是我要的回答 -具理事
The minister is now with the vice president
部長現在和副社長在一起
Do you want to go over and have a look?
你要過去看看嗎？
OK, let's go
好，走吧
Yes, this way please
是，這邊請
walk slowly
慢走
Are you reading nonsense?
你在看胡說八道嗎？
right
对
There hasn’t been much discussion recently
最近都沒什麼討論
very quiet
非常安靜
Seriously, I don't think there's any need to check over there.
說真的，我認為不用檢查到那邊
Do we even have to regulate nonsense?
難道我們連胡說八道都要管理嗎？
Then go and go somewhere else
那你就走，去別的地方
Okay, that's what I'm going to do
好，我就打算這麼做
When I become an agent, I want to go to the sales team
等我當上代理，我想去營業組那邊
Staying in the PR team is not conducive to promotion
待在公關組不利於升遷
Look at you, you are so ambitious
看看你，野心真大
Don't always meet your sister
別總是跟姐姐見面
You won’t get back together
你們又不會復合
She has another partner
她有再婚對象了
I was called over by her
我是被她叫過去的
How is that? So irresponsible
那是怎樣？好不負責任
It is irresponsible for her to seek me out
她找我才是不負責任的行為
Go find your senior to investigate
去找你前輩追究
She's drunk, don't go to her
她是因為喝醉了，你別去找她
You should take the initiative to reject her
你應該主動拒絕她的
Why?
憑什麼？
I'm lonely too
我也很孤單啊
I shouldn't have introduced them
我不該介紹他們認識的
Can't stand it
受不了
We have a dinner party today
今天要聚餐
How is this?
這是怎樣？
I can't tell whether you are happy or not
我分辨不出你們高不高興
nice
正啊
It is to commemorate the inauguration ceremony of personnel regardless of qualifications.
是為了紀念舉辦 資格不拘人員就職儀式
The room chief gave instructions in the hope that all groups can unite
室長下指示希望各組能團結
Inaugural ceremony for persons with no qualifications and the unity of our group…
和我們組別的團結…
There is a huge correlation!
有很大的關聯性！
Let's get ready for a dinner party, everyone
大家準備去聚餐吧
Which restaurant should I book?
要訂哪間餐廳呢？
He didn't even answer
他也不回答一下
Three groups
三组
Who can come to the party today?
今天有誰可以參加聚餐？
What about the rest?
其他人呢？
I already have an appointment
我已經有約在先了
My mother is feeling unwell and has an appointment to see a doctor today.
我媽媽身體不適，預約今天要看醫生
Where is Agent Xu?
許代理呢？
I can go
我是可以去
You'd better go home today
你今天還是回家吧
Go back and take a nap and then take a shower
回去睡一覺，然後洗個澡
good
好
Then our group will have a dinner party at noon tomorrow instead.
那我們這組就以明天中午聚餐代替
OK
好的
She is a young lady with no qualifications
是資格不拘小姐
I am Section Chief Meng Zhejun
我是孟哲俊科長
right
对
Thanks to you, we are going to have a dinner
多得你，我們要去聚餐
goodbye
再见
Hello
你好
Aren't you three groups going to have dinner together?
你們三組不聚餐嗎？
We will have a lunch party tomorrow instead
我們改成明天中午聚餐來代替
Why?
为什么？
One person said that he wanted to accompany his mother to see a doctor. This must be a lie.
有一個人說要陪媽媽看病 這肯定是騙人的
The other person was asked to go home to rest and wash up.
而另一個人被叫回家休息盥洗
Obviously this is to welcome you into the company, really
明明這是要歡迎你進公司的，真是的
What?
什么？
So do you want to have dinner with our group?
那你要跟我們組一起聚餐嗎？
Is this okay?
這樣可以嗎？
Can not be done
不行啊
Damn it, then what are you asking?
可惡，那你問什麼？
Hello
喂
Do you want to drink with Team Leader Song? serious?
你想和宋組長喝酒嗎？認真？
In no mood
不想
I didn't consider that
我沒考慮到那一點
it's a pity
真可惜
You are the only wage earner I know who likes to have dinner together.
你是我認識的人之中 唯一喜歡聚餐的打工仔
Li Sejiang also likes it
李瑟蔣也很喜歡
Cao Ya public relations…
曹亞公關…
Then you have worked hard today too
那你今天也辛苦了
See you next time
下次見
Yes, Agent Jaemin, you have worked hard too
是，才旻代理，你也辛苦了
move
快走吧
The section chief too
科長也是
Go quickly
快走
Meng…
孟…
(Representative Kim Hee-young)
（金熙英代表）
Do you have an appointment tonight?
你今天晚上有約嗎？
So what to eat?
所以到底要吃什麼？
- You can eat whatever you want. - Find any place.
-隨便吃什麼都可以 -隨便找個地方
Then let's go eat grilled pork belly
那我們去吃烤五花肉吧
-Roasted pork? The opposite one? -right
-烤五花肉？對面的嗎？ -對
Yes, the one opposite
對，對面那間
- Let's go . It's cheap and delicious there.
-走吧 -那邊便宜又好吃
Yes, we have an appointment
是，有約了
Xiao En, do you want to eat pig's feet?
小恩，你要吃豬腳嗎？
Add some disc soba noodles
加點圓盤蕎麥麵
Then why do you have to go to work?
那你們為什麼要上班？
Just to make money?
只是為了賺錢嗎？
I hope my abilities are also appreciated
我希望我的能力也受到賞識
So I'll be a senior executive
所以我會成為高階主管
Is she self-actualizing?
她是在自我實現嗎？
Or schizophrenia?
還是精神分裂？
how?
怎樣？
Don’t you understand Shi Rong yet?
你還不了解世容嗎？
Only 1% of employees become senior executives
只有1%的員工能成為高階主管
The chances are slim, almost impossible
機會微乎其微，幾乎是不可能的事
But just you as a girl?
但就憑你一個女生？
The representative is also a girl.
代表也是女生啊
The business belongs to their family, regardless of gender.
企業是他們家族的 可以撇除性別不論
wrong
不對
If Representative Lin were a man, he would have inherited the company long ago.
如果林代表是男人，早就繼承公司了
How could he be the head of the strategy department?
怎會當策略本部長？
Yes, Seyong is that kind of place
沒錯，世容就是那種地方
I still have to do gymnastics at the company
在公司還要做體操
Shi Rong is gradually changing
世容也漸漸在改變了
This time the new chief public relations officer is also a girl.
這次新來的首席公關長也是女生
She is someone else found on behalf of others.
她是代表另外找來的人
There has never been a woman starting from the grassroots in Shirong
世容從來沒有女性從基層做起
An example of finally becoming a senior executive
最後當上高階主管的例子
I'm going to set a precedent!
我就要來開先例！
As long as you drink, you can talk to me no matter how big or small you are.
你只要一喝酒，對我說話就沒大沒小
What are you doing
你在做什麼？
watch video?
看影片？
Social climate is really changing
社會風氣真的在改變
Watching a movie by yourself during a dinner party?
竟然在聚餐時自顧自地看影片？
It's so boring, you guys keep talking about the same topics over and over again
太無聊了，你們又反覆聊著 同樣的話題
good
好
Since we're bored now, let's repeat the same itinerary and go to the second stall.
既然現在很無聊 我們就反覆同樣的行程，去第二攤吧
-Give it back to me -Don't make trouble
-還給我 -別鬧
You all want to go to the second stall, right?
你們都要去第二攤吧？
-Then I'm looking for Team Leader Chi. -What?
-那我要找池組長來了 -什麼？
-Team leader? -yes
-池組長？ -對啊
That's right
沒錯
It seems that the room manager did not invite Team Leader Chi
看來室長沒有邀池組長
Team Leader Song and Team Leader Cui are both there, right?
宋組長和崔組長都在那裡吧？
They should go to a high-end bar, and of course they can't ask out Team Leader Chi.
他們應該去高檔酒吧了 當然不能約池組長
By the way, is the dinner party between the three groups over?
話說三組聚餐已經結束了嗎？
They want to have a lunch party tomorrow instead
他們要改成明天中午聚餐
Really?
真的吗？
It's different because the team members are younger
組員比較年輕就是不一樣
Not a typical dinner party
不走典型的聚餐
that's what i want
那就是我想要的
Brother, please transfer me to the third group
大哥，把我調到三組吧
Let me transfer there first
先讓我調過去吧
By the way, Jae Min
對了，才旻
My innate sixth sense tells me
我與生俱來的第六感告訴我
Will you date that young lady who has no qualifications?
你會和那個資格不拘小姐交往
How about it? Am I too sharp?
怎麼樣？我太犀利了嗎？
No, what is he interested in?
不是吧，他是看上哪一點？
Cai Min’s vision is not high
才旻的眼光不高
She is within the qualification range
她在合格範圍內
She looks quite cute
她長得挺可愛的
Agent Kim, you shouldn't comment on other people's appearance.
金代理，你不應該評論他人的外貌
Would you be happy if someone said you looked like a gangster ?
如果有人說你一副流氓樣 你會開心嗎？
Hey, do I look like a gangster?
喂，我看起來像流氓嗎？
you just look ugly
你只是長得醜
So who is your ideal lover?
所以你的理想情人是哪一型的？
Angelina Jolie in "Smith vs. Smith's Wife"
《史密夫決戰史密妻》的 安潔莉娜裘莉
Stop it
少來
Anyway, don’t make reservations for me if you want to renew your stall.
總之續攤不要預我
If you want to renew your stall, please use this card. Team Leader Song just gave it to me.
想續攤的人用這張卡吧 剛才宋組長拿給我的
Okay, let's go, go quickly...
好，你走吧，快走…
- It's really dirty. - Take it.
-真是髒死了 -拿去
Please, I've taken a shower
拜託，我洗過澡了
Come on, let's have one last drink and then go.
來，我們乾了最後一杯就走吧
(PS Bank, Corporate Card, Shirong)
（PS銀行，公司卡，世容）
welcome
歡迎光臨
I say you
我說你
Do you know how many years we haven’t seen each other?
你知道我們到底幾年沒見了嗎？
You pretend a little bit that you're happy to see me
你稍微假裝見到我很開心
-is it hard? -i'm happy to see you
-很難嗎？ -我見到你很開心
Came here again…
再次來到這裡…
It's also very happy, it's still the same.
也很令人高興，還是老樣子啊
Time seems to have paused here
這裡的時光彷彿暫停了
We all drank like crazy here when we first became journalists.
我們剛成為記者的時候 都在這裡瘋狂喝酒
Do you remember?
你還記得吧？
Really, you want to invite me to drink with you?
真是的，要邀我一起喝啊
It feels good to drink it by yourself
自己喝感覺也不錯
Hello
喂
In that case, why did you come to me?
既然如此，你為何找我來？
Just drink it yourself, right?
你自己來喝就好了，不是嗎？
how is your day?
你過得好嗎？
not good
不好
I've been through all kinds of storms
我歷經各種大風大浪
Had a very hard time
過得非常辛苦
Then why did you come back suddenly?
那你怎麼會突然回來？
I thought you wouldn't come back
我以為你不會回來了
This one
這個啊
I may be a little tired
我可能有點累了
No matter what achievements are made there
在那裡不管達成什麼成就
I'm just a stranger
我都只是一個異鄉人
There's a feeling of not being able to fit in
有種無法融入的感覺
It turns out you came back to recharge your batteries
原來你是回來充電的
I understand what you mean
我懂你的意思
But why is it Se Rong?
但為什麼偏偏是世容？
You probably can’t stand it very much, right?
你應該會很受不了吧
Yeah?
是吗？
forget it
當我沒說
It's really a good place to spend time
那裡確實是一個打發時間的好地方
Anyway, I'm glad to meet you.
總之我很高興見到你
Oh my god
天啊
It’s really a great honor for Goo Yi Jung to come to me.
具伊貞居然來找我，真是莫大的殊榮
I don’t have many friends that I’m in contact with either.
我也沒幾個有在聯絡的朋友
Really?
真的吗？
That should be an honor for you
那應該是你感到榮幸才對
Come on, cheers
來，乾杯
- I'm honored - OK
-我很榮幸 -好
Let’s start with warm-up exercises
我們先從熱身運動開始
Raise your knees past 90 degrees
將膝蓋抬高超過90度
Hands slapping the knees alternately
雙手交互拍打膝蓋
Don't move too fast
動作不要太快
-What are you doing? -I ate too much and couldn't breathe
-你們在做什麼？ -我吃太多，喘不過氣
Feel like vomiting
感覺快吐了
Would that be better?
那樣會好一點嗎？
Don't talk to me, I'll really spit it out
你不要跟我講話，我真的會吐出來
Hey, shut your mouth
喂，閉上你的嘴巴
There seemed to be something at the corner of your mouth just now
剛才你的嘴角好像有東西
I'll smoke one
我就抽一根
Um?
嗯？
Something's not right with Yoo Jae-min
柳才旻不太對勁
Hello
喂
It's almost time. Go and smoke one.
時間差不多了，你快去抽一根吧
- Go quickly - I don’t want to smoke
-快去 -我不想抽啊
go ahead
去吧
- Really - Put your hands on your waist
-真是的 -把手放在腰上
Spread your feet shoulder-width apart
雙腳張開與肩同寬
Hello
喂
Didn’t you quit smoking?
你不是戒煙了嗎？
Originally it was
本來是啊
What's wrong? Are you worried?
怎麼了？你有心事嗎？
Hard to say
不好說
how?
怎样？
Don't you want to say it?
你不想說嗎？
No, I don't want to say it
不是我不想說
That's it anyway
反正就這樣
Really
真是的
Hey, you are really acting out today
喂，你今天真的特別反常
what happened?
到底怎麼回事？
Why did you suddenly start smoking?
你怎麼突然抽起煙了？
Do you think of your old lover?
難道你想起了你的舊情人嗎？
What kind of cliche is that?
那是什麼老套的說法？
Um
嗯
What? Really?
什麼？真的嗎？
Who was your old flame?
你的舊情人是誰？
-Why should I tell you? -Because we're playing the truth game
-我為什麼要告訴你？ -因為我們在玩真心話遊戲
What? So sudden?
什麼？這麼突然？
Yes, this kind of game is fun only when you are caught off guard.
對啊，這種遊戲本來就要 來個措手不及才好玩
-Right? -Yeah, it just needs to be unexpected.
-對吧？ -對啊，就是要令人出乎意料
Where did we first meet?
我們初次相遇的地點？
San Diego
聖地牙哥
what? When did you go to San Diego?
什麼啊？你什麼時候去聖地牙哥的？
Is this a problem?
這是問題嗎？
Is this the answer?
難道這是回答嗎？
I went there after I was discharged from the army. Next question
我退伍後就去了，下一題
how did you guys meet?
你們怎麼認識的？
We met by chance while walking on the street
走在路上偶然認識的
Be more detailed
說得詳細一點
It was raining that day
那天下著雨
We stayed in the same hotel
我們住在同一間酒店
then fall in love
然後就墜入愛河
I heard you were joking. Are you lying?
聽你在作故仔，你是騙人的吧？
Yes, he is lying, this must be fake
對，他在騙人，這肯定是假的
Hey, why am I the only one playing the truth game?
喂，怎麼只有我在玩真心話遊戲？
There's nothing to ask. We know everything about each other, right?
沒什麼好問的 我們對彼此瞭如指掌，對吧？
Of course we have no secrets
當然，我們沒有秘密
-Every relationship of hers is short-lived . You don't have to give in too much.
-她每段戀情都很短命 -你也不遑多讓
At least longer than you
至少比你久
Whoever likes you, date them and then get rid of them first
誰喜歡你，你就跟誰交往 再率先甩掉人家
If my feelings for them don't deepen, then I should break up.
我對他們的感情沒有加深 那就應該分手才對
When you agreed to date, did you really like the other person?
你答應交往時，是真心喜歡對方嗎？
Probably to the extent that I have a good impression of him
大概是有好感的程度
It’s also magical to stop at a good feeling
止步於好感也很神奇
Yes, how could this happen?
是啊，怎麼會這樣？
I really hope someone can teach me
真希望有人來教教我
Because you only date trash
因為你只跟廢物交往
Hello
喂
Don't you know
你是不是不知道
What does it feel like to love someone?
愛一個人是什麼感覺？
Do you know it well?
那你很了解嗎？
Of course, I understand very well
那當然，我超級了解
What does that feel like?
那是什麼感覺？
like this
就像這樣
You can feel it just by looking at it
光是看著就感受得到
Just by looking at each other, you can understand everything
四目相交就能心領神會
Needless to say
無須多言
Do you have someone you like?
你有喜歡的對象吧？
Is it me?
是我嗎？
If so
如果是的話
What do you want?
你想怎麼樣？
Hey, look at his expression, he looks like he is about to perish.
喂，你看他的表情 一副要亡國的樣子
Wait, it’s very unpleasant to think about it.
等等，仔細想想很不爽啊
Hey, sister, I like you, shouldn’t you be grateful?
喂，姐姐我喜歡你 你不是應該心懷感激嗎？
Yes, I'm very grateful
對，我感謝得不得了
It's so hot here, I feel like my heart is going to jump out
這裡一陣火熱，感覺心臟要跳出來了
Really
真是的
So talented
那麼才旻
What do you think about me?
你覺得我怎麼樣？
Do you want to date me?
要跟我交往嗎？
No, sister
不要，姐姐
Do you mind if I refuse?
我拒絕，你不介意吧？
Why did you reject me? Can you tell me why?
你為什麼拒絕我？ 可以告訴我原因嗎？
You two are really sick
你們兩個真的有病
because of you
因為你
It's really not my type
實在不是我喜歡的類型
I gotta go
我要走了
Can I go?
我可以走了吧？
Can I ask you another question?
那我可以再問你一個問題嗎？
what is the problem? If you want to ask, ask quickly, I'm really tired
什麼問題？要問快問，我真的好累
You have never been in love
你一直沒有談戀愛
Could it be
難道
Is it because of her?
是因為她嗎？
I am leaving
我走了
Hey, please understand the situation
喂，你搞清楚狀況
What do you think that means?
你覺得那是什麼意思？
Did he acquiesce?
他默認了嗎？
whatever
隨便啦
you…
你…
Either you speak clearly
你要麼把話說清楚
Otherwise, let it go decisively
不然就果斷地放下
It’s been decades
都已經幾十年了
Crazy woman, oh my god
瘋女人，天啊
Hey, it's not like that, it's really not
喂，不是那樣的，真的不是
If I still have feelings for him
如果我對他還有感覺
I just heard him say that I'm not his type. I should have felt like a bolt from the blue.
剛才聽到他說我不是他喜歡的類型 我應該會覺得晴天霹靂吧
There are already tears in your eyes
你眼裡已經含著淚水了
Damn it, I just said no
可惡，我就說不是了
I gotta go
我要走了
-Hey -so what?
-喂 -又怎樣？
You just have to let go decisively
你才要果斷放下
(Yu Zhen, mother has returned to Korea)
（俞真，媽媽回韓國了）
(You didn’t answer the phone, so I sent you a message)
（你沒聽電話，所以我傳訊息給你）
(Be sure to call me when you have time)
（有空務必要打給我）
Today was tough
今天辛苦了
Won't
不會
Let's go
我們出發吧
Why are you here? I heard that you are very busy recently
你怎麼會來？聽說你最近很忙
Yes, I am indeed busy
對，我確實很忙
Although I am very busy, this is the only time I can chat with my daughter
雖然很忙，但這是我唯一 能和女兒聊天的時間
Are you free right now?
你現在有空嗎？
What's wrong? Why do you look unhappy?
怎麼了？你怎麼一臉不開心？
What happened?
出了什麼事嗎？
No, it's spam
沒有，是垃圾訊息
It's really annoying and annoying
真的好討厭又好煩
sounds like lunch meat
聽起來像午餐肉
How about we have ham for dinner?
我們晚餐吃火腿怎麼樣？
No, I want to eat fish
不要，我要吃魚
mackerel
鯖魚
Yu Zhen, do you know that mackerel is difficult to predict?
俞真，你知道鯖魚難以揣測嗎？
Why?
为什么？
Because there is a song with the lyrics "It's unpredictable whether it's sunny or rainy"
因為有一首歌的歌詞是「晴雨難測」
You told cold jokes again
你又說冷笑話
What's wrong? Why does your expression look like this? Did anyone bully you?
怎麼了？你的表情怎麼這樣？ 有人欺負你嗎？
(Se Yong)
（世容）
morning
早晨
(Shi Rong, qualifications are not limited!)
（世容，資格不拘！）
Hello everyone
大家好
I'm from the Public Relations Team 3 of the Public Relations Office of the Business Strategy Headquarters.
我是經營策略本部公關室公關三組的
Park Yoon Joo
朴允珠
I used to work in a PR agency
我之前在公關代理公司工作
When I heard Se Yong
當我聽到世容
For the first time, we should recruit employees solely based on their resumes.
要破天荒地 單純以個人履歷來招聘員工
I thought I couldn't miss the opportunity, so I applied.
我心想不能錯失機會，於是就應徵了
After I graduated, I worked in the general affairs team
我畢業後就在總務組工作
It took about three to four years
大概做了三至四年
Later, I switched to a company that produces corporate newspapers and periodicals.
後來換到一間製作企業報刊的公司
I was originally from the general affairs team
我本來是總務組的人
But there was a shortage of manpower at the time, so I started writing reports
但當時人手短缺，我便開始撰寫報道
That’s when I started to get involved in the public relations industry
我就是從那時候開始接觸公關行業的
(Qualifications are not limited, recruitment of experienced personnel will be finalized, public relations schedule)
（資格不拘，具經驗人員招聘 最終錄取者，公關日程表）
(Public relations office, represented by Park Yun-soo)
（公關室，朴允昭代理）
(Appeared in the CNS program character documentary "Partners")
（出演CNS節目 人物紀錄片《夥伴》）
Does anyone know why there is a CNS documentary filming on Park Yun-soo’s schedule ?
有誰知道朴允昭的行程當中 為什麼有CNS的紀錄片拍攝？
It was Team Leader Song who arranged it, and Shengxi rushed to do it.
是宋組長安排，然後勝熙搶著做的
I do not know how?
我怎麼不知道？
Yes, why don’t you know?
對啊，你怎麼不知道？
Didn’t Seunghee tell you?
勝熙沒告訴你嗎？
I heard that Agent Park refused once but they kept pushing her.
聽說朴代理拒絕過一次 但他們一直逼她
Who watches CNS documentaries these days?
最近誰還會看CNS的紀錄片？
Those high-level people
那些高層
Hello, team leader, morning
組長好，早晨
morning
早
Team Leader Chi, would you like to make you a cup of coffee?
池組長，要幫你沖杯咖啡嗎？
-Agent Park -Yes
-朴代理 -是
Did you come into the company to help me make coffee?
你進公司是來幫我沖咖啡的嗎？
Just do what you have to do
做你該做的事情就好
And I don't drink coffee
而且我不喝咖啡
Caffeine gives me heart palpitations
咖啡因會讓我心悸
I drink
我喝
2 tablespoons each of coffee, creamer and sugar
咖啡、奶精和糖各兩匙
That is three-in-one instant coffee
也就是三合一即溶咖啡
sorry to bother you
麻煩你了
You are not my team leader, I will not help you rush
你不是我的組長，我不會幫你沖
What do you do early in the morning?
你一大早有什麼事？
that…
那个…
I heard Agent Park
我聽說朴代理
Declined to shoot CNS documentary
婉拒拍攝CNS的人物紀錄片
I want to ask
我想請問
Do you know the reason why Agent Park refused?
你是否知道朴代理拒絕的原因
As far as I know, you can refuse
據我所知是可以回絕的
Yes, of course you can refuse
對，你當然可以拒絕
But…
可是…
why?
為什麼呢？
You seem to think it's easy to get on a wireless station
你好像以為要上無線台很容易
Actually not
實際上不是的
Besides, the title is pretty good.
況且頭銜取得不錯啊
Everyone says you are the hope of the Republic of Korea
大家都說你是大韓民國的希望
Just let the organizer handle it.
你就讓承辦人自行處理吧
Why go out of your way to ask here in person?
何必特地親自走來這裡問？
It's just because they can't handle it that I came here personally.
就是因為他們處理不了 我才會親自來一趟
Pool leader
池组长
Did you assign her work?
你有指派她工作嗎？
Is that why you are so busy? Is it because you are too busy?
所以你才會忙不過來嗎？ 是因為太忙了嗎？
I need to confirm her itinerary
我要確認一下她的行程
My purpose for filming a TV documentary
我去拍電視紀錄片的目的
Is it to enhance the company's image?
是為了提升公司形象吧？
The target customer group is people in their 20s
目標客群是20多歲的人
Then don't do it through TV documentaries
那不要透過電視紀錄片
I will find someone who specializes in interviewing wage earners.
我會去找專門採訪打工仔的
Well-known YouTube channel to shoot
知名YouTube頻道來拍攝
Main audience groups of CNS character documentaries
CNS人物紀錄片主要的觀眾客群
Is the audience over 50 years old
是50歲以上的觀眾
This is not in line with the target customer group
這不符合目標客群
And the YouTube channel is dedicated to discussing career development
而YouTube頻道專門在探討職涯發展
Can conduct more in-depth interviews
可以進行更有深度的採訪
That probably won't work
那恐怕行不通
In the company
在公司
There is a long-established process
有一套長久以來固定的流程
Team Leader Song
宋組長
I will confirm this when I come back later.
這件事我待會回來會再確認
It's time for us to have a team leader meeting
我們該去開組長會議了
Will she still make a CNS documentary?
她還要拍CNS的紀錄片嗎？
Is there any reason why she didn't take the photo?
她有理由不拍嗎？
Every time we were willing to bear the full production fee, they were unwilling to shoot.
我們每次願意承擔全額製作費 他們都不願意拍
This time he agreed.
這次卻一口答應了
Let's get it straight. Who are you doing this for?
我們直接把話講明吧 這麼做是為了誰？
Vice president?
副社長嗎？
Don’t we have clear goals and objectives?
我們不是有明確的目標與目的嗎？
You disrespected her too much just now
你剛才也太不尊重她了
What did you say?
你說什麼？
- I won't force her - Then let me do it
-我不會勉強她 -那我來吧
She is my team member
她是我的組員
I remember I'm more senior than you, right?
我記得我比你資深吧
they arrived
他們到了
Representative Xu
徐代表
Hello
你好
Our team leader’s previous meeting will end later
我們組長前一個會議稍後才會結束
- Over there please - Okay
-那邊請 -好的
-The representative- is here
-代表 -來了
-Excuse me, Miss Shin Ji -hyo-Yes
-不好意思，申智孝小姐 -是
Who is responsible for Sirdis?
西爾迪斯是哪位負責的？
it's me
是我
It would be nice if it was, but it's not me
如果是的話就好了，但不是我
The team leader must handle it personally
組長要親自處理
Is Team Leader Chi personally responsible?
池組長要親自負責嗎？
Very good
太好了
Leave some time for me another day
改天留點時間給我
I invite you to dinner
我請你吃飯
Of course, eat what you like
當然，是吃你喜歡吃的
Nowadays, the younger generation tends to do a lot of things in a short time
現在年輕一代 傾向在短時間內做很多事情
- That leads to... - Then I want roast beef.
-那導致… -那我要吃烤牛肉
They often lack attention…
他們經常缺乏注意力…
Feel sorry
抱歉
It doesn't matter
沒關係
in daily life
在日常生活中
For example, while they were waiting for the bus...
舉例來說，他們在等巴士的時候…
Hello
你好
(Section Chief Meng Zhejun)
（孟哲俊科長）
Where are you?
你在哪里？
You want this, right?
你要這個吧？
right
对
Pantry
茶水間
What do you do after get off work?
你下班後要做什麼？
What's wrong?
怎么了？
Are there any good movies showing?
有好看的電影上映嗎？
right
对
"August Photo Studio" is re-released
《8月照相館》重新上映
That one again?
又是那部？
Thanks
谢谢
It’s a big deal, Jae Min
大件事了，才旻
Someone is posting nonsense about the eligibility-free program
有人在胡說八道 發布關於資格不拘計劃的事
Any idea that employees select candidates through blind testing is a lie.
什麼由員工透過盲測來選人 都是騙人的
It is said that the senior management selected the person for publicity.
據說是高層為了宣傳才挑人的
I thought it was weird from the beginning
我一開始就覺得有古怪
Se Yong is cleaning up her image
世容正在洗刷形象
Making a big fuss just to admit someone
為了錄取一個人把事情鬧得很大
Using people with no qualifications to promote themselves?
利用沒有資歷的人來宣傳？
Se Yong’s public relations office is not what it used to be.
世容的公關室不如從前了
What image enhancement does this enhance?
這能提升什麼形象？
This kind of pomp and circumstance is no longer about walking in through the back door , but coming in openly.
這種排場已經不是走後門 而是光明正大走進來了
I heard that the public relations office didn't give her any instructions about her work.
聽說公關室也不交代她工作
She has no qualifications
她既沒有資歷
-She's not working either . She will be dumped after her one-year contract expires.
-也沒在工作 -一年合約到期後，她應該會被拋棄
Do you want to send people with excellent qualifications to the factory?
是要把資歷優秀的人派去工廠嗎？
No one went to vote at all
根本就沒人去投票
-Who voted? -I didn’t vote either
-誰有投票？ -我也沒投
What? Why was she admitted?
什麼？她憑什麼被錄取？
There are a bunch of people in our company who don't know how to read the discussion forum
我們公司有一堆人不會看討論區
There is no point in discussing it here
在這裡討論沒意義
The first article about the eligibility-free program was posted around 3:10 p.m.
第一篇關於資格不拘計劃的文章 是下午3點10分左右發的
It's 3:45pm now
現在是下午3點45分
But the number of messages has exploded
但留言數已經爆炸了
I have never seen such a big commotion since I joined the company.
我進公司以來 從來沒見過這麼大的騷動
I think we need to confirm the facts first
我想我們要先確認事實
Ms. Park Yun Zhao
朴允昭小姐
Selected by employees through blind testing.
是員工們親自透過盲測選出來的
right?
沒錯吧？
probably
應該是吧
Nothing wrong?
沒有錯吧？
Isn't that a matter of course?
那不是理所當然的嗎？
Is not it? I do not know
難道不是嗎？我不知道了
Where is the team leader?
組長呢？
In the morning, he talked with the director of "Daguo Daily"
他上午和《大國日報》的局長
We went drinking together with Houji.
還有厚佶一起喝酒去了
we need to check the facts
我們需要查核事實
Didn't he listen? He won't listen
他沒聽吧？他一定不會聽
The call you made was not...
您所打的電話未…
He 's not very good at checking his phone when he's drinking with reporters.
他跟記者們喝酒的時候 本來就不太會看手機
Brother Zhejun, where do you think they are?
哲俊哥，你說他們在哪裡？
Gwanghwamun Octopus Shop
光化門章魚店
(Who is eligible to vote under the Free Plan?)
（誰有參加資格不拘計劃投票？）
(I asked people in the same group and no one voted)
（我問了同組的人，沒有人去投票）
(There are many comments but many people did not vote)
（留言有很多 但沒投票的人比較多）
( Why should she admit the majority of people who didn’t vote ?)
（沒投到票的人佔多數 她憑什麼錄取？）
Really are
真的是
What's up?
什么事？
This is a nonsensical discussion forum for Se Yong
這是胡說八道的世容討論區
(Any idea that employees select candidates through blind testing is a lie)
（什麼由員工透過盲測來選人 都是騙人的）
Related articles have also begun to appear in the company discussion forum.
公司討論區也開始出現相關文章了
If we just ignore...
如果我們直接忽視…
That shouldn't work, right?
應該不行吧？
Damn it
該死
Just listen and say, "You've made a mistake."
你聽好，就說「你們搞錯了」
"The company is not qualified to do this kind of thing. The plan is indeed chosen by you personally."
「公司沒有做這種事 資格不拘計劃確實是你們親自選的」
Just deal with it
就這樣處理
Immediately write a statement and submit it to the Human Resources Office
馬上撰寫聲明稿交給人力資源室
Post to the company forum during off-hours
在下班時間發布到公司討論區
This matter must be resolved quickly
這種事必須速戰速決
Before get off work?
下班前嗎？
right
对
What's wrong?
怎么了？
It's not like you haven't dealt with it before
你又不是沒處理過
This kind of thing should be covered up quickly to avoid causing a bigger fuss.
這種事要迅速掩蓋過去 以免鬧得更大
Haven't you seen her resume?
你没看过她的履历表吗？
She works in digital PR
她是做数码公关的
Let her join your group!
让她去你们那组啊！
Honestly, I recommend the person who doesn't meet the qualifications.
老实说，力推那个资格不符的人
-Obviously it's you, because that way it's topical - Hey!
-明明就是你，因為那樣才有話題性 -喂！
Hey, this is her job
喂，这就是她的工作
Become an Advocate for the Eligibility-Free Program
成为资格不拘计划的代言人
That's why she was admitted
那就是她被录取的理由
if her qualifications are always in dispute
如果她的資格總是受到爭議
That's not good for her or the company.
那對她或公司都不是好事
For her sake, this matter must be brought to an end quickly
為了她著想，必須趕緊讓這件事落幕
You go
你走吧
Team leader
組長
This is not true, is it?
這不是真的吧？
( Answers to questions related to recruitment regardless of qualifications are provided here )
（在此針對資格不拘招聘 相關疑問做出回答）
(The recent false news that qualifications are not limited to the recruitment process may cause our company...)
（最近資格不拘招聘流程的 不實消息可能造成本公司…）
It's not that bad overall
這整體來說沒有那麼糟
But where to focus…
但焦點要放在哪裡…
I'm going to get off work
我要下班了
good
好
It’s not clear where the focus should be.
焦點要放在哪裡不是很明確
I thought so
我是這麼想的
How about highlighting this part?
強調一下這個部分如何？
- And don't want this - this way?
-然後不要這個 -這邊嗎？
right
对
-Okay, I got it -Okay
-好，我知道了 -好
besides…
還有…
Then we need to use something else here
那這邊要用其他東西
- Want to make up for it? -Yes, it would be better to make up for it here.
-來補嗎？ -對，這邊補一下會比較好
-Fix this side or... -Yes
-補這邊或是… -是
-I'm going to get off work -Okay
-我要下班了 -好
Content and pictures, think about which one is better...
內容和圖片，想想哪個比較好…
yes
是
( Answers to questions related to recruitment regardless of qualifications are provided here )
（在此针对资格不拘招聘 相关疑问做出回答）
Too much content has been deleted, right?
內容也刪減太多了吧
Almost half deleted
幾乎刪掉了一半
The team leader’s explanation should be brief.
組長交代要簡短一點
so things get worse
所以事情變得更糟了
Everyone criticized the company for uploading the statement after working hours
大家都抨擊 公司在下班時間上傳聲明稿
I don’t think this can be called a statement either.
也認為這稱不上聲明
Borrow it
借過一下
Excuse me
不好意思
I borrowed it, sorry
借過，不好意思
-Sorry . What did you hit?
-抱歉 -撞什麼啊？
The train door is closing
列車門要關了
Alas
唉唷
Sorry, lend me a hand
不好意思，借我過一下
Stand in a little bit
站進去一點
The person who came in regardless of his qualifications was selected by the senior management.
那個資格不拘計劃進來的人 是高層選出來的
This is a shocking fact told to me by a colleague in the public relations office
這是公關室的同期告訴我的驚人事實
There was an article before about several team leaders in the public relations office.
之前有篇文章說公關室幾個組長
Are you going to quarrel because your qualifications are not limited?
因為資格不拘計劃吵架吧？
I heard that thing is true
聽說那件事是真的
After she joined the company, no group in the PR office wanted her.
她進公司後 公關室沒有任何一組想要她
Yes, no surprise
對，不意外
An online university has produced a talent
網絡大學出了個人才呢
Sure enough, the truth will eventually come out
果然真相終究會水落石出
(Is Shirong recruiting employees for publicity?)
（世容招聘員工是為了做宣傳嗎？）
Why should I waste four years in college?
我為什麼要浪費四年讀大學？
If there is a next life
如果有下輩子
I also imagine her entering the company with a diploma from an online university
我也想像她靠網絡大學的文憑進公司
Hey, did you know that person was chosen by the senior management?
喂，你知道那個人是高層選的嗎？
Yeah, I heard that, it's crazy
嗯，我聽說了，簡直瘋了吧
The team leaders of the PR office even had a big fight over this.
公關室的組長們還為此大吵了一架
We were raped by an unqualified person
我們被一個不夠資格的人
-It's making a big fuss -That's what I mean
-鬧得雞飛狗跳 -就是說啊
The atmosphere was tense
氣氛都被搞僵了
It's so annoying to be in the same company as her
跟她待在同一間公司真討厭
Really, so embarrassing
真的，好丟臉
Really, the phone keeps ringing
真是的，電話響個不停
Their sense of smell for gossip is as sharp as a bedbug's
他們對八卦的嗅覺真靈敏 跟臭蟲子一樣
Hello? Hello
喂？你好
Hello, Reporter Park, yes
你好，朴記者，是
it's not like that
不是那樣的
When did you see it?
你什麼時候看到的？
-No -Really, what are you talking about?
-沒有 -真是的，你在亂講什麼？
It was just a little farce
那只是小小的一場鬧劇
- That was a misunderstanding - Yes
-那是個誤會 -對
We have published our official position in the company discussion forum
我們已經在公司討論區 發布官方立場了
-There are indeed many creative messages - why don't you believe it?
-的確有很多創意十足的留言 -你為什麼不相信呢？
correct
沒有錯
But you shouldn’t add fuel to the fire, right?
但你不應該火上加油吧？
I wish you could revise the wording a bit...
希望你稍微修改一下措詞…
okay, thank you
好的，謝謝你
-What? Hello? -goodbye
-什麼？喂？ -再見
Hello?
喂？
hateful
可惡
Who was in the public relations office at the same time?
那個公關室同期是誰啊？
Thanks to that article, things got even bigger again.
拜那篇文所賜，事情又鬧得更大了
Where has Agent Liu gone? Was it a good thing he did?
柳代理那傢伙去哪裡了？ 是不是他做的好事？
- No way - Damn it
-不會吧 -該死
-Hello?
-喂？
The wrong use of one person caused such a big disturbance
錯用一個人造成這麼大的風波
I can hear the calls from the PR office coming and going from here.
我在這都聽得到 公關室此起彼落的電話聲
The atmosphere in their office must be tense
他們辦公室的氣氛一定很僵
"Se Yong's plan to not restrict qualifications caused controversy"
「世容的資格不拘計劃引發爭議」
"The hot potato in social platforms for wage earners"
「打工仔社交平台內的燙手山芋」
Oh my god, it’s in the news. Has Saeyong finally made the headlines on the portal?
天啊，還上新聞了 世容終於登上入口網站頭條了嗎？
It made the news after all. It’s really embarrassing.
終究還是鬧上新聞了，真丟臉
All the parties involved are here, have you had enough of talking?
當事人都來了，你聊夠了吧？
How do you look at other people's screens?
你怎麼看別人的螢幕？
Then don't let me see it
那你就不要讓我看到
How is she?
她是怎樣？
It's too much
真是過分
(Office of the Director of Public Relations Office)
（公關室室長辦公室）
Now
現在
The chief was furious
本部長氣得火冒三丈
This incident even appeared in the daily newspapers
這件事還登上了日報
And it’s a daily newspaper that the vice president reads every day!
而且還是副社長天天都會看的日報！
Now everyone says this is reverse discrimination
現在大家都說這是逆向歧視
What to do now?
這下該怎麼辦？
You hire someone who is not qualified
你錄用那個不夠資格的人
What are you going to do now?
現在打算怎麼辦？
You shouldn't say she's not qualified enough, right?
你不應該說她不夠資格吧
Everyone says that
大家都這麼說啊
Why don't you say anything?
你們怎麼都不說話？
What are you going to do?
你們打算怎麼做？
About that employee
關於那位員工
The employee who caused controversy
那位引起爭議的員工
Tell me about it
你們說說看
Can we fire her?
我們能夠解僱她嗎？
(Is Shirong recruiting employees for publicity?)
（世容招聘員工是為了做宣傳嗎？）
(There are a lot of discussions on the social platforms of migrant workers)
（打工仔社交平台議論紛紛）
( Weird recruitment where lack of qualifications becomes a qualification ?)
（不具資歷變成一種資歷的 怪異招聘？）
(Suspicion of inappropriate recruitment by Se Yong)
（世容不當招聘疑雲）
(Before, they advertised that they only select elites)
（之前還四處宣傳他們只挑精英）
(The person who came in regardless of qualifications was selected by the senior management)
（那個資格不拘計劃進來的人 是高層選出來的）
Thanks for your hard work
辛苦了
(The characters, events, groups, organizational backgrounds, etc. in this drama are purely fictitious. We hereby inform you)
（本剧之人物、事件、团体、组织 背景等纯属虚构，特此告知）
Subtitle translation: Wu Jingyi
字幕翻译：伍静怡